benhogangolf.com 2018-12-18

# Terms and Privacy – Ben Hogan Golf

**Privacy Statement**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

 **Collection of your Personal Information**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company does not read any of your private online communications.

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company and Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company family of Web sites.

 **Use of your Personal Information**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company collects and uses your personal information to operate the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company and its affiliates. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company, in order to determine what Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company, or the public.

 **Use of Cookies**

The Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company pages, or register with Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company site or services, a cookie helps Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company services or Web sites you visit.

 **Security of your Personal Information**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

 **Changes to this Statement**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company is protecting your information.

 **Contact Information**

Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Ben Hogan Golf Equipment Company at benhogan@benhogangolf.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
